[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
We've built a simple model just relating square feet of living space to price
我们刚才建立了一个简单的模型 解释了房屋售价和房屋面积有所相关
of houses and then we explored some other features like zip codes,
我们还研究了其他一些特征 比如邮政编码
and it's clear the zip codes make a big difference and there's other features,
很显然邮政编码对于房屋售价有着很大影响 也有别的因素影响
bedrooms, that also makes a big difference.
比如说卧室数目 也会对售价产生影响
The question is can we get a better model by including more features, more of these?
那么问题来了 我们能否通过增加更多的特征得到一个更好的模型？
And so let's look at that.
看这里
So we're gonna do here is build
我们在这里要做的就是
a regression model with more features.
建立一个回归模型 它包括了更多的特征
So this is using this bigger feature set that we just described.
所以说这会是我们所说的一个更大的特征集
So the first one I called the sqft_model.
我们把第一个模型叫做 sqft_model (sqft模型)
Let's call this
那我们就把这个叫做
the my_features_model.
my_feature_model (我的多特征模型)
So the my_features_model is again going to take graphlab.linear regression.create.
所以我们这个my_feature_model 还是会用 graphlab.linear regresssion.create 来创建
So we're gonna create it and we're gonna use the training data,
我们会使用 训练数据
just like we did before.
就像我们之前所做的一样
Our target is again going to be the price, just like before.
我们的目标还是和之前一样 预测价格
However, the features here that I'm gonna use are going to be those
不过在模型中 我会用到更多的特征
features that are called my features which I created earlier.
这些特征来自于我创造的my features中
So let's go and execute this.
让我们来执行吧
So now I use more features and it's straining and I think it's done it's done.
所以现在我在用更多的特征预测售价 好了 应该训练完成了
Using those, I forget how many, eight features.
用了我的特征集中的特征 我忘记一共有多少个了 应该是8个吧
I use, let's just print them out here, print my_features.
恩 我现在输入 print my_features(打印 my_feature这个特征集)
So I use bedrooms, bathrooms,
所以说你看到了 我一共用了 卧室 卫生间
square foot of living, square foot of lot, floors and zip code.
客厅面积 占地面积 楼层数目 还有邮政编码
Now we have two models.
所以我们现在有了两个模型
We have the sqft_model and we have my_features_model.
我们有了sqft_model 和 my_features_model
How do they compare in terms of performance?
那怎么比较这两个模型孰优孰劣呢?
So here's what I'm going to do.
那么在这里我要做的是那么在这里我要做的是
I'm going to print the sqft_model.evaluate,
我要打印出衡量模型的结果 通过打印 sqft_model.evaluate
evaluate all my test data.
来衡量我的测试数据的结果
And I'm also going to print
我要做的还有
the my_features_model.evaluate on the same test data.
和之前一样 打印出我测试数据的衡量结果 (通过print my_features_model.evaluate这个命令)
And let's compare, let's see what happened.
让我们开始比较 看看什么会发生
Okay, so to start with,
开始咯
we saw that the biggest error in the simple square foot model was $4 million.
我们可以看到对于简单的sqft_model 最大的误差在400万
Now it's down to $3.4 million, 49, so 3.5 million.
而my_features_model 的最大误差在349万 就当做350万好了
So it went down a bit.
降低了一点
And root mean squared error, the average error,
均方误差也就是误差的平均值
went down from $255,000 as we had over here to a $179,000.
从255000降低到了179000
Now, if you add more and more features, your area is likely going to decrease
如果你添加了更多的特征 你的误差会降低更多
quite a bit more because there's quite a bit of data here and
因为这边的数据量很大
there's lots that you can learn.
你可以从数据中发掘更多的东西
But again, just adding some extra features already helped us with our performance.
话说回来 通过增加一些额外的特征可以使我们模型更加优化
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community